popist.com 2016-11-29

# Idealab | Privacy Policy

Definitions

The term **Personal Information** means information about you that is personally identifiable, such as your name, address, email address, or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. The term **Non-Personal Information** means information that does not personally identify you and cannot be used to contact you or identify you (for example, information about your computer configuration, Software/Site usage, etc.) The term **Information** means both Personal Information and Non-Personal Information.

Questionnaires and Surveys

From time to time, we may ask you to complete questionnaires or surveys, which we use to obtain additional demographic information about our users, to measure and improve the quality of our products and services and to better assess your interests and needs. If we ask you to complete a survey or questionnaire, we will explain how we intend to use the information that you provide to us. You always have the option of not responding to any questionnaire or survey.

Children

Our Site is not directed towards children 13 years of age or under and we do not knowingly collect any information from children 13 years of age or under through the Site.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

Idealab may change this Policy at any time. We will notify you about significant changes in the way we treat your Information by placing a prominent notice on the Site.

Contact Information

If you have any questions about our products, services, or this Policy, or if you need to revise or remove your stored Information, please contact us at [support@idealab.com](mailto:support@idealab.com).

Information Collected

We collect and store Non-Personal Information, including for example site referral information, browsing patterns, technical information (e.g., browser type and version, downloads, and operating system), and general Site use information through standard Internet protocols and logging.

We do not collect Personal Information via the Site without your knowledge. If you do send us Personal Information (for example, by utilizing a feedback page on the Site where you provide your name, email, comments), we may retain such Personal Information for purposes of responding to your email or inquiry, informing you about updates and changes to the Site, and otherwise contacting you regarding the Site.

Use and Transfer of Information

We use Non-Personal Information to better understand the use of the Site, improve and revise the Site based on usage, and for customer support purposes. We also use Non-Personal Information to track product interest and/or downloads.

Disclosure of Information to Third Parties

We may share aggregated Non-Personal Information about our Site with our business partners or the general public. For example, we may share information regarding the daily number of unique users to our Site with potential corporate partners or others.

We may also share the Information we collect from and about you for the following purposes:

  * Your Information may be transferred to anyone who is helping us make the Site available and functional, like technical agents, service providers, other subcontractors, and our affiliates and consultants.
  * We might share your Information during due diligence or in preparation for a sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets, reorganization or liquidation.
  * We may disclose your Information if permitted or required by law or where we believe such action is necessary in order to protect or defend our interests or the interests of our users or business partners

Linked Internet Web Sites

The Site may contain hyperlinks that take you to a third party website, document, file, or other materials. These third party hyperlinked materials may contain privacy provisions that are different from those provided herein. We are not responsible for the collection, use, or disclosure of information collected through these web sites, and we expressly disclaim any and all liability related to such collection, use, or disclosure.

Sale of Assets

In the event that another company acquires all or substantially all of the assets related to the Site or other business of Idealab, we reserve the right to include Information among the assets transferred to the acquiring company.

General

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time, and will do so by posting changes to this Privacy Policy.

The Site is hosted in the United States and are intended for and directed to users in the United States. If you are located outside of the United States, please be advised that we process and store information in the United States and your use of this Site constitutes your consent to and understanding of this processing.

Information that we collect is stored on servers that we manage, using reasonable administrative, technical and physical safeguards designed to protect against unauthorized access or disclosure of data. Please be aware that no data transmission over the Internet is guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

REVISED: March 2016
